Submitting a Translation
Steps are as follows:
1. Fork the Security White Paper repository
2. Clone your forked repository to your computer
3. Make your changes
4. Commit changes and push them up to your forked repository
5. Make a pull request from your forked repository to the original repository
Open your browser and find the Security White Paper repository here:
Click 'Fork' to create your own copy of this repository on GitHub
You may be asked to select where to fork the repository.
So choose the appropriate location, probably your personal account
You can now see your repository, and where it's forked from.
Open your Git client. GitHub for Mac is being used for this tutorial.
Click to add a Git repository.
Select 'Clone'...
Search for the correct repository...
And clone it!
Nominate where you would like it to be cloned on your computer.
Now you are ready to make changes!
Add your translated version of the Security White Paper into the appropriate location
within the cloned repository on your computer.
Now in your Git client, commit your changes to your repository.
Fill in a Summary...
And, optionally, a description.
Click 'Commit'.
Your commit is ready to be pushed up to GitHub.
Click 'Sync'
Now you can click the 'Pull Request' icon to submit the changes made in
your repository back to the original repository.
You can adjust the Summary and Description for your pull request.
Click 'Send Pull Request'.
Success! You've now submitted your translation of the Security White Paper.
Click the link to view it on GitHub.
Now you wait for feedback on your request, or it may just be merged in.
Good luck, and thanks for volunteering your time to help make WordPress
accessible in multiple languages!